Simon Maxwell-Stewart

Software Developer | smaxwellstewart.com

ABOUT

I'm a software developer with 5 years of professional experience. I'm interested in all kinds of visual communication, but my major focus is on developing realtime web apps, with mobile & tablet interfaces. I also have skills in other fields like data analysis and reporting.

EDUCATION

BSc. Physics

University of Oxford | JULY 2010

3 Year Course

A Levels: Maths & Further Maths, Physics & Biology

King's School Worcester | JUNE 2007

2 Year Course

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Mobicow.com | 2014 - CURRENT

Mobicow is a an ad network with a difference, they have built their own custom adnetwork. Working for them has taught me how to make realtime applications at full internet scale.

Web Developer

Freelance | 2012 - 2014

Running my own business gave me a huge amount of responsibility I would not have easily found elsewhere. I enjoyed the pressure of having to make smart business decisions day in day out.

IT Maintenance & Social Media

NHC Institute | 2011 - 2012

Web Designer

Red PR & Marketing | 2010 - 2011

Chef

Winston Churchill Pub - Montreal, Canada (2011)

Saffrons - Worcester, UK (2010)

The Royal Oak - Oxford, UK (2008)

DJ / Club Promoter

Baby Love Bar, Oxford. Ran and performed a profitable student club night.

SKILLS	Javascript	PHP	Wordpress
SNILLS	<i>Javase</i> ipt		** **********************************
	Dootstran		Cyra Admin
	Bootstrap	HTML/CSS	Sys Admin
	Email		Dhone
CONTACT	Email		Phone
CONTACT	Email smaxwellstewart@gr	nail.com	Phone +1 514-898-0189
CONTACT		nail.com	
CONTACT		nail.com	
CONTACT	smaxwellstewart@gr	nail.com	+1514-898-0189
CONTACT	smaxwellstewart@gr Address 349 St. Marguerite	nail.com	+1514-898-0189 References Available on
CONTACT	smaxwellstewart@gr Address 349 St. Marguerite Montreal, CANADA	nail.com	+1 514-898-0189 References
CONTACT	smaxwellstewart@gr Address 349 St. Marguerite	nail.com	+1514-898-0189 References Available on
CONTACT	smaxwellstewart@gr Address 349 St. Marguerite Montreal, CANADA	nail.com	+1514-898-0189 References Available on
CONTACT	smaxwellstewart@gr Address 349 St. Marguerite Montreal, CANADA	nail.com	+1514-898-0189 References Available on